Contact

9729796495 (Home) jd1romero@gmail.com

www.linkedin.com/in/jd-romeromsn-rn-cen-tcrn-a48a8b86 (LinkedIn) www.hcanorthtexas.com (Personal) www.ena.com (Other)

Top Skills

Healthcare
House Supervisor
Emergency Services

JD Romero, MSN, RN, CEN, TCRN

Lead House Supervisor, Patient Advocate, SAMA Instructor at Medical City Alliance

Dallas/Fort Worth Area

Summary

Over 20 years with HCA North Texas. Served in many roles throughout HCA. Anything from post Open Heart Surgery to Heart Transplant to Administration. I have worked at Medical City Dallas, Medical Center of Arlington, as well as Las Colinas and Plaza Medical Center. Now I am proud to say that I'm helping with opening our newest facility....Medical City Alliance.

Experience

HCA North Texas RN,MSN,CHS-III,CEN

Medical City Alliance
Lead House Supervisor
January 2015 - Present (5 years 5 months)
Dallas/Fort Worth Area

Oversee daily operations of facility. Ensure proper patient throughput.

ER at Alliance Staff RN, SAMA Instructor November 2011 - January 2015 (3 years 3 months)

ER Alliance is a provider based emergency room able to meet the needs of anything that the community may require. I work as a staff nurse able to perform all duties as recognized by the ENA. Being with HCA for over 20 years has provided me the opportunity to work in many different modalities. From Open Heart to Heart Transplant, Telemetry, Emergency Services, House Supervisor, and Medical Surgical - I feel I have done much. And even though I do not know everything I feel I have a sufficient grasp to handle multiple projects, diverse situations with successful outcomes. People, great people is what makes great facilities.

Education

Walden University

Master of Science in Nursing, Organizational Leadership · (2009 - 2011)